Part B consists of a coffee shop website consisting of 2 webpages - Home and About Us section.
Home page consist of navigation bar which is contained under nav tags. Header tags have also been used to highlight the headers/titles used in the web user interface, and footer tags have been used as well to create a footer section to mention the name of the creator of website at the bottom of the web page.

Home page also contains an audio clip (coffee sip) that has been attached to add an immersive feature to the website for user using an audio tag to add mp3 file.

About Us page consist of header, footer, navigation tags as well but it also additionally contains section tag to highlight the "About Us information" of the coffee shop.

A single css has been used to style the webpages - home.css

HTML5 Tags used in Part B: <header>, <footer>, <nav>, <section>, <audio>
