Part A consists of a restaurant website consisting of 3 webpages - Home, Menu, and Contact.
All the three pages consist of navigation bar that are styled using css and are created using unordered list and anchor tags for references and to navigate to different html pages.

Menu page consist of a table with images and prices of food items available. So it consists of image tag and table tags with table rows and table data tags respectively.

Contact page provides user with an interface to book reservation using form which was created using form tags, input tags to get input from user such as user name, reservation date, number of people to book reservation for etc. The page also has a submit button that redirects user back to home page.

All the three pages contain favicon as well as link for google api font used in the assignment 1 part A.

A single css file is used -> home.css

All the controls that were required to use were implemented - favicon, table, form, images, hyperlink, button.
