Assignment 2

The website is my professional portfolio which comprises of 3 web pages - Home page, Portfolio page which has an image gallery of some of my course certificates and contact page which consists of email-id, phone number links with the use of 'mailto' and 'tel' options. 

Home page as well as image gallery page consists of divs which presents a column layout structure.

Contact page also consists of icons using font awesome script that can be clicked to access GitHub, LinkedIn, Facebook and instagram social media handles. Clicking on the submit button after entering the required information will redirect back to home page.

Media Query has been implemented in order to edit the navigation bar such that it is presented in a column structure below the width of 768 pixel and image gallery width is set to 100%. 

Tags used: div, img, nav, header, footer, anchor tags, form, input, textarea, h1,h2,h3, p, link, i - icon tags(for font awesome icons).

Bonus: Upon hovering over the grayscale image on home page and certification page, the greyscale filter becomes inactive in order to make the website more immersive.

