Assignment-6

Assignment 6 is a cloud hosting platform created using html, sass/scss. 


SCSS/SASS functions

• Variables have been used in _color.scss to create variables for color. 
• _Config.scss files consist of function set-space to calculate margin and padding values based on iteration of space amounts list consisting of numbers 1-5. The file also contains mixing to set background and text color of button and background of webpage for dark and primary colors.
• _mobile.scss consist of media queries for max-widths: 768px and 500px.
• _utilities.scss file consist of styling of container, card, grid, flex, (to implement css grid and flexbox), button.
• style.scss consist of import of other non-executable scss file, styling for navigation with nesting. Placeholder selector(%header1-2) for h1,h2 header files with same styling attributes extended. Styling of grid column and row layouts for cli section in home page(index.html) and about clouded section in features page (features.html).

Grid/Flexbox:
CSS grid and flexbox functionalities have been implemented in column and row layouts for cli section in home page(index.html) and about clouded section in features page (features.html).
The CLI image takes up two rows and two columns. CLI section comprises of 3 columns and 2 rows.
Features section consist of grid layout as well where first child takes up 3 columns and remaining grids and 2nd child of feature container takes up 2 columns. 
Images in both pages have been justified to end of flex layout.

